#This dictionary is used to make a question bank for the dad joke quiz game

#"question" is the key and "answer" is the value
question_data = {"question": "What do sprinters eat before a race?", #question
    "select your answer": "A) Celery B) A protein shake C) Carrots D) Nothing they fast ", #multiple choice
    "answer": "D", #answer
    "hint": "what is the religious practice of not eating" #Hint
},

{
    "Question": "Air use to be free at the gas station, now its a $1.50. You know why?", #question
    "Select your Answer":  "A) Hard times B) Inflation C) Greedy Gas station owners D) The trying times of 1856 ", #multiple choice
    "Answer": "B", #answer
    "Hint": "the opposite of deflation"#Hint
},

{
    "Question": "How did the man on the moon cut his hair?", #question
    "Select your Answer":  "A) Scissors B) He eclipse it  C) He brought his barber D) With some moon rocks", #multiple choice
    "Answer": "B", #answer
    "Hint": "What is it called when the sun covers the moon"#Hint
},

{
    "Question": "What do a tick and the Eiffel Tower have in common?", 
    "Select your Answer": "A) They're both Paris sites B) They like to stay in one place C) People have to travel to find them D) Both are costly, one to see and one if you don't remove",
    "Answer": "A", 
    "Hint": "Where is the Eiffel tower located"
},

{
    "Question":"What do you call a fish wearing a bowtie?",
    "Select your Answer":"A) A werido B) A confused fish  C) Sofishticated D) A weird flex ",
    "Answer":"C", 
    "Hint":"What is a word for a knowledgeable fashionable person"
},

{
    "Question":"If April showers bring May flowers, what do May flowers bring?", 
    "Select your Answer":"A) Instagram models B) Pilgrims C) Bees D) Pollen season",
    "Answer":"B", 
    "Hint":"Who sailed to the united states"
},

{
    "Question":"What do you call a factory that makes okay products?", 
    "Select your Answer":"A) A dollar store supplier B) A satisfactory C) Your average factory D) Walmart",
    "Answer":"B", 
    "Hint":"What is another way to to say you did a good job"
},

{
    "Question":"What did the janitor say when he jumped out of the closet?", 
    "Select your Answer":"A) Were out of bleach B) I wasn't napping! C) Who locked me in there D) Supplies!",
    "Answer":"D", 
    "Hint":" ____ & demand"
},

{
    "Question":"What did one wall say to the other?", 
    "Select your Answer":"A) How many wholes are they going to put in us? B) Hey is your paint dry yet C) I'll meet you at the corner D) I don't like this new color on us",
    "Answer":"C", 
    "Hint":"What is it called when two edges meet"
},

{
    "Question":"What did the zero say to the eight?", 
    "Select your Answer":"A) Why did you let 7 eat 9 B) That belt looks good on you C) So are you just infinity standing up D) Me and one are going to make 10",
    "Answer":"B",
    "Hint":"What do you use to hold your pants up, that is not suspenders"
},

{
    "Question":"What do you call a poor Santa Claus?",
    "Select your Answer":"A) St. Nickel-less B) A man who's job was automated C) Fired from coca-cola D) Divorced from Mrs. Claus and she got the workshop",
    "Answer":"A", 
    "Hint":"St. Nick"
},

{
    "Question":"What did one hat say to the other?", 
    "Select your Answer":"A) I hope they washed their head B) Looks like he got a bad hair cut again C) Stay here! I'm going on ahead D) The owner has a lot of dandruff",
    "Answer":"C",
    "Hint":"Where do hats go on a person"
},

{
    "Question":"Why was the PowerPoint presentation so desperate to cross the road?", 
    "Select your Answer":"A)  B) C) D) Because he badly wanted to go the other slide",
    "Answer":"D",
    "Hint":"What is a powerpoint presontation made of"
},

{
    "Question":"Why did everyone tell the new computer teacher that he was always extremely confused on Twitter?",
    "Select your Answer":"A) All his tweets were" + '"Chirp"'+ "B) It was probably because he didn't follow C) He made weird hastags D) ",
    "Answer":"B", 
    "Hint":"How do you stay up to date with a page on twitter"
},

{
    "Question":"What is the only reason why a car made by computer manufacturers doesn't last for a very long time?",
    "Select your Answer":"A) You shouldn't ask a fisherman to do the job of a hunter B) An engine doesn't have Ram C) It is perhaps because they have hard drives D) They don't account for oil changes",
    "Answer":"C", 
    "Hint":"if your computer doesn't have a SD it has a ___"
},

{
    "Question": "Why was the computer scientist very upset when his computer got affected by a virus?", 
    "Select your Answer": "A) Because now it needed console-ing B) Because people will find out about his Malware practice C) Because it ran someware D) Because it was a terminal illness",
    "Answer": "D", 
    "Hint": "What is another word for console or command line"
},

{
    "Question": "Why is the A spider the absolute expert in navigating the internet?", 
    "Select your Answer": "A) Because they can type quickly B) Because they know all about the web C) Because they have some many eyes D) Because they took a comp sci class with Peter Parker",
    "Answer": "B", 
    "Hint": "What do spiders use to trap their prey"
},

{
    "Question": "Why did the functions stop calling each other?", 
    "Select your Answer" : "A) Because they had constant arguments B) Someone broke their function their call C) They had conflicting data types D) They had syntax errors",
    "Answer": "A",
    "Hint": "What goes inside a function"
},

{
    "Question": "What do you call a skinny ghost?",
    "Select your Answer": "A) Casper on a diet B) King Hamlets boot camp recruit C) The phantom menace D) BOOLEAN",
    "Answer": "D",
    "Hint": "What kind of operators are AND, OR, NOT or AND NOT"
},

{
    "Question" : "Why does Yoda's code always crash?", 
    "Select your Answer" : "A) He can't type with his fat fingers B) Programing skills weren't taught in Jedi school C) Because there is no try D) ",
    "Answer": "C", 
    "Hint": "do or do not"
},

{
    "Question": "Why do anarchists like functional programming?", 
    "Select your Answer": "A) Because it has no state B) Because Object oriented programing has to much structure C) There's no hierarchy D) Procedural Programming has to many rules",
    "Answer": "A", 
    "Hint": "what are New jersey, ohio, nevada"
},

{
    "Question": "What's the second movie about a database engineer called?",
    "Select your Answer": "A) Boring B) Free Guy 2: Wrath of the database C) SQL D) Ex Machina 2 the attack of the database ",
    "Answer": "C",
    "Hint": "domain-specific language used in programming and designed for managing data "
},

{
    "Question": "Why didn't the client tip the server?",
    "Select your Answer": "A) Because they didn't have enough cache B) Their card declined C) The server gave bad service D) It was included in the bill",
    "Answer": "A", 
    "Hint": "something in computer science that stores data so that future requests for that data can be served faster;"
}